[{"answer": "That is the forecast.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "What is the probability now given all the computer projections that you've been looking at, what is the probability today that come Sunday, New York City could get hit by this hurricane in a direct hit?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Yes, especially if it's a little bit left of the city.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Even if it's just a little offshore?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Piers, it's been quite a week in the dismal swamp and earthquake and now with this change over the last 24 hours and the storm track looks like it would come right across Virginia Beach and Hampton Roads area where there are 1 million people that will be experiencing hurricane force winds.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Are you prepared, do you think, as a state for what may be coming?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, absolutely.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Are you concerned about what may happen if it hits directly on New York City?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Don't like this one at all.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "What are you feeling about it?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Well, New York obviously doesn't get hit by hurricanes very frequently.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Do you think New York City is ready for this?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Absolutely, Piers.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Is that what happens?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Well, evacuation is a very tricky thing, because we've seen instances before -- it's a very expensive proposition.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Isn't that leaving it a bit late?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, it seems that the rebels were working on rumors rather than fact, places they thought they had Gadhafi surrounded, turned out not to be that.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Nic, what's latest over there now?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "This is a smart guy who's incredibly paranoid.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "So what is your gut feeling about how he may be trying to get out of there, without being spotted, caught or whatever?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "You know what's really weird here is, I went over to the Rixos Hotel here, the hotel Matthew and Jomana were held up in by Gadhafi's gunmen, the hotel that we stayed in six weeks earlier on in the year, the government minders who were working with us then, I met one of those at the gate today, this afternoon.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Do you have any kind of estimate for that?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "I'm not sure.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Presumably, you'll be dealing with it in your normal fearless way, will you, Jack?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Why do you say that about him?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Well, of course -- I mean, you never know.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What kind of effect can that have on a company that's so s successful?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "You know what, he was always interested in every technical electronic gadget there was in the world.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "What was he like in those days?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Steve Jobs definitely.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Who would be more successful if you hadn't met each other?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "I'm still an Apple employee.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "You're still an Apple employee, aren't you?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "I think the check -- I don't even see it, but I think it's a couple hundred bucks every two weeks.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "How much do you get?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "It should be one dollar1.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Do you have any interest in the company?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "My wife and I really aren't big stock traders.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Do you have a stake in the company at all these days?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "What gadgets do you work?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Number one, I use my computer with the full typing keyboard.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Are you an Apple consumer?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Apple, absolutely.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "It is an Apple computer?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I have had non-Apple products many, many times.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Do you have an iPod?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "His way of thinking -- I call it a higher level.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "What is it about Steve Jobs that made him the genius he became?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "He's very gracious.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "You know, it's products -- oh, just like Steve Jobs, I grew up thinking the technology products are the hottest area of the world.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Why do they mean so much to you?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Normally I would said, well, 20 years is too far to predict and some very futuristic ideas like computers are going to be conscious and they're going to speak just like you and me.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "What do you think it's going to be going to?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "But I don't know if that is going to happen in 20 years.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "They won't be able to host shows like this, will they?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "It looks like it to somebody who sees it.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "What is that?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Can you actually tell the time on it?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "He's been sick at different stages.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Have you spoken to Steve since he got sick?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Very good friends.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "So you and Kathy are just good friends, yeah?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "It isn't like you are ruthless or you're not ruthless.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Does he have it?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Giving mankind the most useful, helpful tools we've ever had in our history.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "But in terms of what you know of him, what do you think he'd like the legacy to be, the Steve Jobs legacy to be?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "It's hard to say, because a computer used to be a device on its own.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Was the computer, which you were very instrumental in producing -- is that going to be the greatest invention of the last millennium?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "I don't think we can stop the effect of the future, the future that we've created giving them devices.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "And they should be out playing konkers and soccer and stuff like that, shouldn't they?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "110825pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 661}]